Krishna Nahak

Bengaluru, Karnataka, India Sr DevOps Engineer at Zivame

Summary

Experienced DevOps Engineer with a demonstrated history of working in the apparel and fashion industry. Skilled in Technical Support, apache2,nginx, Elasticsearch,AWS. Strong engineering professional with a Master of Computer Applications - MCA focused in Information Technology from Kalinga University, Raipur.

Experience

Sr DevOps Engineer at Zivame
April 2018 - Present (1 year 2 months)

DevOps Engineer at Zivame.com April 2016 - March 2018 (2 years)

System Engineer at Zivame.com October 2013 - March 2016 (2 years 6 months)

Customer Support Engineer at Mars Infosystems
November 2011 - September 2013 (1 year 11 months)

Education

Kalinga University, Raipur Master of Computer Applications - MCA, Information Technology, 2013 - 2016 Berhampur University, Berhampur Bachelor's degree, 2010 - 2013

Krishna Nahak

Bengaluru, Karnataka, India Sr DevOps Engineer at Zivame

Linked in Recruiter

Profile Notes and Activity (2)

4/22/2019—View by Ravisankar G

4/22/2019—InMail sent by Ravisankar G (Accepted)